regalassets.com 2019-04-09

# Privacy Policy - Regal Assets : Regal Assets

Your privacy is important – Regal Assets is dedicated to protecting yours. Any information we collect is used only to provide you with better services to process your purchases, manage your account and increase your benefit for frequenting our site. We take privacy seriously and as such we take precautions to ensure that none of your privacy rights are violated.

####  **SECURING YOUR PRIVACY**

Our website is a Norton standard secured server powered by VeriSign with an up to date SSL certificate utilizing the exact same online security measures as Bank of America, Citibank, Ally Bank and all major financial institutions. Your private information is never shared with unauthorized parties and is stored in our fully encrypted database giving you absolute security on the most sensitive information that you submit.

####  **PROTECTING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Regal Assets has implemented a number of security procedures to secure protection of our client personal information. Your personal information is contained within securely controlled networks and can only be accessed by employees with the appropriate level of access. Any personal information shared by our employees is transmitted through a secure connection and is safely stored in the Regal Assets encrypted database.

####  **PROTECTING YOUR PERSONAL EMAIL**

All e-mails that are sent out from authorized Regal Assets representatives are sent from a secured server increasing the protection of your private information. Generally all e-mails will contain an opt-out link which you can click to have your name removed permanently from our e-mail list. Regal Assets does not send unsolicited e-mails and will only add you to our e-mail list if you have requested specific information. We value your privacy and will never share your e-mail address with an unauthorized Regal Assets representative.

####  **COOKIES AND TRACKING**

We utilize cookies and tracking pixels to increase our productivity and overall client experience. A cookie is a small data string that is written on your computer hard drive by a web server. (A web server is the computer that hosts a website and responds to requests received from your computer). Cookies can play an important role in providing a great customer experience using the web. Among other things, cookies enable a website to maintain information when a user’s web browser requests a series of web pages. Without cookies, for example, a website owner may not be able to recognize that a user just completed the first step during an ordering process so that the second step can be presented.

Cookies generally hold information, including data strings that contain a unique user ID which allow our website and our affiliates, agents and partners, to customize your experiences and gather information relevant to what you may be interested in. For example, cookies allow us, and others who place and access cookies on our website, to deliver advertising and other content specific to your interests, keep track of your purchases and alert you to new products or promotional opportunities based on your current services.

Information gathered from cookies also helps us understand how our affiliates, agents and partners are performing and provides website usage information to support customizing and improving our website. We also use cookies to help verify the identity of a website user or to recognize you as a registered user and remember your settings and preferences. You can manage cookies by using features and functions available on most Internet browsers. For example, most browsers will allow you to choose what cookies can be placed on your computer and to delete or disable cookies.

We also collect identifiable information through the use of tracking pixels. A tracking pixel is a transparent graphic image (usually 1 pixel x 1 pixel) that is placed on a web page and, in combination with a cookie, allows for the collection of information regarding the use of the web page that contains the tracking pixel. We use tracking pixels to tell when an advertisement has been clicked on or otherwise interacted with, track the web traffic of affiliates, agents and partners of Regal Assets and use that information to judge which advertisements are more appealing to users and which affiliate, agents and parters are successful with their marketing efforts. With tracking pixels and cookies our affiliates, agents and partners who have referred business to Regal Assets are able to access limited private information such as first name, IP address, potential investment amount and the state or region of the referral who accessed our website. Affiliates, agents and partners have access to this limited private information so that they can fine tune and tailor their individual marketing campaigns toward specific demographics. In all cases, we use third-party service providers to help us collect and analyze this information.

Our website contains web beacons in the form of clear .gif files, which are electronic images that allow for the collection of information about your interactions on our sites. Web beacons may be used to place advertisements, to understand website traffic patterns and the number of visitors to our website, and to measure the effectiveness of advertisements or email advertising messages.

####  **PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES**

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any change in how we use your personal information we will notify you by means of a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. If we change or update this privacy policy, we will update the website so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use and disclose. We encourage you to periodically check back to stay completely up to date on our latest privacy policy practices.
